We'll call it over the record.
It's going to be in my city council for Monday, October 16th, 2023.
With two proclamation to claim October 2023 is domestic violence awareness.
Motion.
Thank you.
Parker.
Hi.
Sandra.
Williams.
Hi.
Thank you.
Three proclamation to recognize the Susan Puerto Risi.
Renee Gisler.
Rick Kelly.
We're Joe Woody Greenfeather.
Brad Morse.
Michael Smith.
And Johnson Walters.
With our military service.
Second.
Parker.
Hi.
Williams.
Sandra, are you here for these?
Amy.
You want to do a picture of us holding them in the shirt?
You're all about public speaking.
Four proclamation to the personal persons.
Yeah.
That was the program.
Yep.
Come to the podium.
I'll put for public input.
You get three matches.
Put it on the board there.
Parker.
I'm going to email this too.
The cut off was like 3,800.
I helped a man out to say, let me start.
This is my first time.
And it's not going to be my last.
I have a lot of things to say.
I've been asked to come to City Council before, but I didn't think that I could say anything
under three minutes because I wanted to win it.
And then, not too long ago, someone said, well, he can't lead legitimate.
He've never been to City Council.
So, here I am.
I'm here today about Darrell Jackson.
Then he was the face of homelessness in Ottawa,
first I've ever been here sooner.
But I was diagnosed with cancer in 2001,
not every year of the 12th, last year of 2022.
I've been sick since June 1,
but it didn't stop me from helping my homeless people on the ground.
I did it in between my illness.
So, I've had two major open one surgeries this year and I'm one cancer free
and still recuperating.
So, thank you.
Okay, so I'm here about I can say that I'm responsible for planning up the homeless, the chronic, all the chronic homeless people.
The problem that we had in February of 2021 in South, South Maine, over in South Maine, Billy Ash, Josh, Josh Raider, Stephen Warley,
Sarah Jackson, Henderson Warley, and so I met two of these people at the Chippery Homeless Shelter that the New Hope Shelter threw up in February of 2021 because of the dangerous weather.
And I was working behind the scenes with Tony Holden on a project, just a volunteer project, when he started looking online at Facebook or social media for alternatives to the homeless Shelter here.
And I was working on a, I was working on him most of been worrying of a suggestion that the fury of tribe used their 9,000 dollar COVID grant.
So they got, they got a grant to turn the country close into a COVID over-plus shelter.
And I knew that that wasn't going to be necessary, so I sent information to be in as a plan B to get our people out of homelessness during the winter weather.
But I met Darrell at the shelter, and I went there with a survey to see what type of a need we had, whether we had a need for a homeless Shelter, and to see what the people that were there needed once the shelter closed.
And Darrell was one that I met at the shelter.
He was the face of homelessness in Ottawa County.
There isn't a person that I've spoke with that had to purchase him a meal or a cup of coffee.
Or offered a ride while he lived homeless in those conditions that...
by email due for three years behind.
Bill Koch and a condemned building with no water,
a electric restroom in my, is that through minutes?
Yes.
Oh, shoot.
Okay, I'm asking you, here today, he's been rescued.
He's got a beautiful home that he's lived in for two years.
He's called his own finances.
During after I met a report to APS that he needed help
on February the 16th, 2021,
a month and a half later, the city of Miami's five-tick
in his citation for your native public and that's something
he had no control over.
And because business was done by him,
and because he was still being in his mail.
And he's today, he's been on health as well.
He's owned his own property for two years.
He got his driver's license.
He got a woman's bank and he purchased an automobile.
So I can go back to work.
And I'm asking that the city forgive this citation.
And the word for is a rest because if it gets pulled over,
his trunk will get found in, you know, when people lose everything
that he has.
You know, I've asked Ben, I've asked her mayor, and I'm here.
Ben told me that you, that he works for the embodiment
of the city council and the e-make the decision.
And I'm here asking you to forgive this citation.
Or something, again, this is why I did get him
in mental health for 15 months after that citation.
So it's been a long term.
Thank you for.
Thank you, really.
Thank you.
Bye.
Brian Bliss.
Second.
I'm sorry.
Who is first on that?
Do I?
Parker.
Hi.
Six.
Minutes for the October 2nd, 2020 meeting.
Motion.
Take it.
Parker.
Hi.
Cender.
Williams.
Hi.
Don't go.
I'm John.
The clerk.
18.
Disc golf cages.
A surplus and authorizing.
We offer for sale, scrap, or destroyed.
You have related signing authority to the city manager.
It doesn't mean.
Yeah.
We have.
I don't know if you guys are playing this off.
We'll do this here.
A couple of times.
Kevin.
I'm going to call one day and say, hi.
We have exactly.
Can't just.
And.
I'll let him look at him.
I kind of hated the ear that.
I went to look at him.
And they're real rusty.
And he said.
The flooding down park.
It.
Over the years.
Some of them were like.
Right against the ground.
But.
So they have to.
That.
And they said, so people have shown interest in purchasing them, so it's probably time to go.
They were here for over 30 years.
We just gave you also a critical too.
Brian, is that from the Veterans Park?
Is that right?
Oh, it's the river.
Yeah.
They're not going to replace him.
Is that just something to get a long time ago?
And they've been sent in surplus for a long time.
They did.
That's exactly what it was for.
Okay.
That answered, Michael.
I saw that.
I didn't know if that was the, that was the one north there.
So where will they be posted for sale?
The discuss is, they thought that you find out what the advice material would be.
What the price would be for waste and then to sell to some.
Do you have a list?
Well, after the discuss is the ban.
They go over the auction side.
We'd be notified when they're put on there.
Okay.
We got this three little call.
Yeah, because I got a lady.
I got a call because she's been calling me about this.
I got to make sure she's aware.
Oh, she is.
All right.
Thank you.
I'll make a motion.
Perfect.
Sender?
Hi.
Williams?
Double.
Hi.
Hey.
Clear abandoned and unclined bicycles as surplus and authorizing.
We offered for sale, scrap or destroyed.
Get related signing authority to the same.
Andrew is doesn't mean.
The, the bicycles.
You guys.
I'm just an I do.
But I guess it's.
People just abandoned bikes.
And it's almost like some of these bikes are disposable.
And at least we'll bring them back.
And they're engaged.
And they stack up.
Well, I got a call.
A couple of few weeks ago.
And we were going to see what you go ahead.
And when I was asking a question, it's like sell for very low.
When we try to sell here.
Anyway, we just need approval.
So we can try to decide what we can do.
I have a question.
Are you these bikes viable?
Like, still good.
Right.
I'm sick.
Some of them are.
You're the ones that are recovered by the police.
In the stack.
here outside the city center. Probably most of them are stolen. And then just abandoned, but nobody's ever come to the land.
So we're about to exceed the limits of the principle hold.
We're over falling into the garage now. They certainly have huge data in there.
So we're going to ask them, because Christmas is right on the corner.
And we may have some kids in town that have different organizations give toys and stuff.
We can go into that, or is that allowed? If we had a five-one see or something that was given away.
So I remember what they did. They never waited to do it. Nobody is on them.
But they'd be on Kim or maybe on the website.
But a lot of sites. One money for all bikes must have.
So that's what they did. According to HD years ago, they did that with an individual that referred to bikes.
They just came and bought one. There's a lot.
They can kind of take surplus parts of some and maybe make from 50 bikes, make 10 bucks.
I feel like that's kind of a trend with you see a lot of big people ride no small bikes like they just walk by.
They see a bike, they drive it for a while and then leave it.
Kind of like the winnable scooters, but they're not done by bike.
Exactly. They don't need that credit card for that.
Thank you, Washington.
Take it.
Perfect.
Sunder.
Hi.
Williams.
Guy.
And Uncle.
Hi.
Mayor's nomination to appoint Corey Stutz to the moment down town of Regervent Authority in DRA.
The place in Rome, Stoke, turn to expire 8.29 at 24.
Coach.
Say it.
Sunder.
Hi.
Williams.
Can request for a community crisis centre to allow and to allow them to display purple
bows while the lamp host for domestic violence awareness.
Motion.
What?
Telling it.
Sorry.
She's ready.
You can go ahead if you want.
Take it.
Sunder.
Williams.
Hi.
Welcome.
Another new business.
Many of which have risen since the post in this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 mayor council committee announcements.
14 city manager.
Good team adjournment.
Sorry.
One of them turns.
On that.
Yeah.
Center.
Right.
Wait a second.
Go.